# **Onayemi Samuel**

Software Developer

(+234) 806 131 3253 Onayemi18@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/onayemi-samuel https://github.com/onayemi Lagos, Nigeria

**Summary:** Driven Web Developer with experience working on multiple enterprise level development projects in the Higher Education Industry. Passionate about building responsive user friendly, and accessible products. Proven record of exceptional teamwork, communication and leadership.

## **SKILLS**

Photoshop
CSS, Styled Components
VueJs, ReactJs, JavaScript
Laravel, NodeJs, C#.Net, Wordpress
MongoDB, Mysql, MSSQL Server

#### **EDUCATION**

Lagos State Polytechnics HND, Computer Science 2011

## **Udemy Degree**

NODEJS & PROJECTS COURSE 2022
React Styled Components (V5) 2022
C#.Net Course 2023

**REACTJS & PROJECTS COURSE** 2022

## **Udemy Degree**

**Python COURSE** 

In View

#### **OPSWAT. Academy**

Introduction to Critical
Infrastructure Protection 2022

### **PORTFOLIO**

https://onayemi.github.io/portfolio/

#### **PROJECTS**

http://gen218singleshangout.com/ https://zarephathwidows.com https://www.mfmlekkiyc.org/ https://mfmgvva.com

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## FullStack Developer, Remlex Technologies

February 2019 – Present | Lagos Nigeria

My responsibilities involve creating the database, be involved and participate in the overall application lifecycle, collaborate with front-end developers with instruction with API

## FullStack Developer, Indent Resource Solution

August 2017 - May 2019 | Lagos Nigeria

My responsibilities involve design the database for the application, be involved and participate in design and implementation of the application and inteprete technical and functional design the overall application lifecycle.

## **Software Developer, TEXTNIGERIA**

March 2016 – June 2017 | Lagos Nigeria

Collaborate with my team to building reminder portal application, subscription portal application, be involved and participate in the overall application lifecycle Collaborate with backend

Developers, define and communicate technical and design requirements, build high-quality reusable code that can be used in the future, collaborate with multidisciplinary team of designers, developers and system administrators

## Backend Developer, Hologram Africa

September 2015 - February 2016 | Lagos Nigeria

My responsibilities involve creating the Database for vehicle authentication.